John A. Lomax and Alan Lomax papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Correspondence, 1925-1952 and undated
  - Subseries III: Alan Lomax, 1935-1969 and undated (Box-folder 3/115)
    - August 1937 (Box-folder 3/124)
      - Anna Blanche McGill to Alan Lomax, 1937-08-30
        Josephine McGill
      - Alan Lomax to Rosa Warren Wilson, 1937-08
    - September 1937 (Box-folder 4/125)
      - John Fred Williams to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-01
      - Alan Lomax to Kay Dealy, 1937-09-01
      - Alan Lomax to Kay Dealy, 1937-09-01
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-02
      - Shelby Kash to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-02
      - Ann Cobb to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-04
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail and Delivery Division, 1937-09-04
        Bill of lading
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1937-09-04
      - Howard Brockway to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-05
      - Alan Lomax to Anna L. Bertram, 1937-09-08
      - Alan Lomax to Ova O. Haney, 1937-09-08
      - Alan Lomax to Anne Blanche McGill, 1937-09-08
      - Eric T. Clarke to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-10
        Association of American Colleges
      - Harold Spivacke to Eric T. Clarke, 1937-09-15
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-18
      - Leonard Greene to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-18
        Sam Fox Publishing Co.
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-18
      - Eric T. Clarke to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-20
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Eric T. Clarke, 1937-09-22
      - Ova O. Haney to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-22
      - Suzanne Comhaire-Sylvain to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-23
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-23
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-24
      - Alan Lomax to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-27
        Shipping acknowledgement
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-27
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-28
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-09-29
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-09-30
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-16
      - W.C. Bond to Presto Recording Co., 1937-09
        Library of Congress
    - October 1937 (Box-folder 4/126)
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-01
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Mail and Delivery division, 1937-10-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1937-10-02
      - Ova O. Haney to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-06
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-06
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-07
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-08
      - Harold Spivacke to Rosa Warren Wilson, 1937-10-11
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-15
      - Alan Lomax to Railway Express Agency, 1937-10-16
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1937-10-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-20
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Mail and Delivery Division, 1937-10-21
      - Bess Alice Owens to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-24
      - Rosa Warren Wilson to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-25
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10-26
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-10-28
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-10
    - November 1937 (Box-folder 4/127)
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-11-01
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-11-01
      - B. E. Arthur to Alan Lomax, 1937-11-01
        Weston Electrical Instrument Corp.
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1937-11-02
      - Lincoln Thompson to Harold Spivacke, 1937-11-03
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1937-11-04
      - Alan Lomax to Herbert Putnam, 1937-11-04
      - Sidney Robertson to Harold Spivacke, 1937-11-09
      - Harold Spivacke to Mr. Bond, 1937-11-19
        Library of Congress superintendent of buildings
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Chief Clerk, 1937-11-19
      - Alan Lomax to Bess Alice Owens, 1937-11-26
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1937-11-29
    - December 1937 (Box-folder 4/128)
      - Lincoln Thompson to Library of Congress, 1937-12-01
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1937-12-10
      - Lincoln Thompson to Harold Spivacke, 1937-12-11
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1937-12-11
        Hoosier Folklore Society
      - Harold Spivacke to Lincoln Thompson, 1937-12-17
      - Harold Spivacke to Paul G. Brewster, 1937-12-21
      - Lincoln Thompson to Harold Spivacke, 1937-12-23
    - January 1938 (Box-folder 4/129)
      - Clay Walters to Alan Lomax, 1938-01-03
      - Lincoln Thompson to Harold Spivacke, 1938-01-06
      - Alan Lomax to Lincoln Thompson, 1938-01-07
      - Alan Lomax to Lincoln Thompson, 1938-01-14
      - Alan Lomax to Clay Walters, 1938-01-14
      - Clay Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-01-20
        "The Range of the Buffalo"
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1938-01-21
      - Alan Lomax to Lincoln Thompson, 1938-01-22
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1938-01-22
        Ohio and Indiana 1938 recording trip
    - February 1937 (Box-folder 4/130)
      - Alan Lomax to Lincoln Thompson, 1938-02-01
      - Alan Lomax to Charles G. Ritter, 1938-02-01
        RHR Hand-Built Gramophones
      - Alan Lomax to Clay Walters, 1938-02-03
      - Frank M. Thompson to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-04
        Sherman, Texas, Chamber of Commerce
      - Charles G. Ritter to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-08
      - Alan Lomax to Mary Elizabeth Barnicle, 1938-02-11
      - Alan Lomax to Charles G. Ritter, 1938-02-11
      - Alan Lomax to Paul G. Brewster, 1938-02-12
      - Irene Whitfield to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-15
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-20
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1938-02-23
      - George E. Simpson to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-23
      - Chick Ritter to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-23
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-25
      - Stith Thompson to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-26
      - Alan Lomax to Charles G. Ritter, 1938-02-26
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-02-27
      - Alan Lomax to Edwin Fagel, 1938-02-28
      - Alan Lomax to L.B. Stoutt, 1938-02-28
      - Alan Lomax to Samuel P. Bayard, 1938-02-28
    - March 1938 (Box-folder 4/131)
      - E.S. Bayard to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-01
        Pennsylvania Famer
      - Charles G. Ritter to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-02
      - R.J. Coar to Harold Spivacke, 1938-03-03
        Radioscriptions
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1938-03-03
      - Harold Spivacke to R.J. Coar, 1938-03-04
      - E.C. Ball to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-05
        To John A. Lomax but Alan Lomax answers
      - Alan Lomax to H.M. Belden, 1938-03-07
      - Alan Lomax to Louise Pound, 1938-03-07
      - Alan Lomax to Mabel Neale Hunter, 1938-03-07
      - Alan Lomax to Edith Dell Hopkins, 1938-03-09
      - Alan Lomax to Lawrence W. Chappell, 1938-03-09
        West Virginia University
      - Alan Lomax to H.L. Ridenour, 1938-03-09
      - Alan Lomax to E.C. Ball, 1938-03-09
      - Alan Lomax to John Harrington Cox, 1938-03-12
      - Edith Del Hopkins to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-13
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-03-15
      - Mary Agnes Brown to Herbert Putnam, 1938-03-15
        Folk song recital, with acknowledgement by Librarian's office
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-15
      - Herbert Putnam to Mary Agnes Brown, 1938-03-16
      - Lee Lamar Robinson to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-19
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1938-03-21
      - Samuel P. Bayard to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-22
      - Harold Spivacke to Lee Lamar Robinson, 1938-03-23
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Disbursing Office, 1938-03-29
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1938-03-29
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail and Delivery Division, 1938-03-29
      - Charles G. Ritter to Alan Lomax, 1938-03-30
    - April-May 1938 (Box-folder 4/132)
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-04-01
      - Mary R. Rogers to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-01
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-04
      - William A. Myers to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-04
      - Ross F. Lockridge to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-04
      - R.J. Coar to Harold Spivacke, 1938-04-07
      - John M. Umble to Stith Thompson, 1938-04-07
        Goshen College (Indiana)
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-04-07
        Postcard
      - Helena Huntington Smith to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-08
      - Harold Spivacke to R.J. Coar, 1938-04-12
      - Library of Congress Music Division to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-12
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-13
      - John W. Boehne, Jr. to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-14
        U.S. House of Representatives
      - Edward Keating to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-18
        Labor newspaper
      - Mrs. Rudolph Roy to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-20
      - Lee Lamar Robinson to Harold Spivacke, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Helena Huntington Smith, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Robert L. Day, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to R.W. Fray, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to John M. Umble, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Doyle Joyce, 1938-04-21
        Works Progress Administration, Federal Writers Project
      - Alan Lomax to Dora Ward, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Josephine Caney, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Mrs. Rogers, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Aunt Phoebe Elliot, 1938-04-21
      - Alan Lomax to Dora Bryant, 1938-04-21
        Mrs. Thomas M. Bryant
      - Ross F. Lockridge to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-22
        Indiana University Foundation
      - Alan Lomax to Mrs. Rudolph Roy, 1938-04-22
      - Aunt Phoebe Elliot to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-22
      - James F. Broussard to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-22
        Louisiana State University
      - Alan Lomax to John W. Boehne, Jr., 1938-04-23
      - Charles G. Ritter to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-23
      - Alan Lomax to Ross F. Lockridge, 1938-04-25
      - Alan Lomax to James F. Broussard, 1938-04-25
      - John M. Umble to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-29
      - Paul G. Brewster to Alan Lomax, 1938-04-30
      - Helena Huntington Smith to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-05
      - Dora Bryant to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-10
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1938-05-13
      - Alistair Cooke to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-17
        British Broadcasting Company; photocopy, original is in correspondence file
      - J.M. Gevedon to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-17
      - Alan Lomax to Olin Downes, 1938-05-19
        New York World's Fair
      - Elizabeth B. Costello to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-21
      - Alan Lomax to Elizabeth B. Costello, 1938-05-26
      - Alan Lomax to John M. Umble, 1938-05-26
      - Maurice Roberts to Alan Lomax, 1938-05-26
        Crown Foto Features
      - Alan Lomax to Olin Downes, 1938-05-26
      - Alan Lomax to Dora Bryant, 1938-05-26
      - Alan Lomax to Paul G. Brewster, 1938-05-26
      - Alan Lomax to Ralph S. Boggs, 1938-05-26
      - Alan Lomax to Maurice Roberts, 1938-05-27
      - Alan Lomax to Mary Elizabeth Barnicle, 1938-05-28
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Flammer, 1938-05-31
    - June 1938 (Box-folder 4/134)
      - Felix Greene to Herbert Putnam, 1938-06-01
        British Broadcasting Company; photocopy, original in correspondence file
      - Alistair Cooke to Herbert Putnam, 1938-06-01
      - Alistair Cooke to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-01
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-06-02
        Photocopy, original in correspondence file
      - Alan Lomax to Ralph S. Boggs, 1938-06-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1938-06-03
      - Harold Spivacke to Alistair Cooke, 1938-06-03
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1938-06-03
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-06
      - Alan Lomax to John Hammond, 1938-06-06
        Columbia Recording Corporation
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-06-08
        Proposal for Michigan 1938 recording trip recording trip
      - Margaret Marquis to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-08
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Music Division, 1938-06-09
        Request for funds for Michigan 1938 recording trip recording trip
      - Robert E. Allen to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-09
      - Irene Whitfield to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-09
      - Alan Lomax to Kay Dealy, 1938-06-13
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-14
      - Alan Lomax to Robert E. Allen, 1938-06-14
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-06-15
      - John Hammond to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-15
      - Marguerite I. Gilmore to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-16
        Bryn Mawr Summer School
      - Harold Spivacke to Librarian of Congress, 1938-06-17
        Newspaper clipping enclosed
      - Alan Lomax to Olin Downes, 1938-06-18
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-21
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-21
      - Alan Lomax to Esther Peterson, 1938-06-21
      - Alan Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-06-22
        Library of Congress Music Division; accession of discs, draft
      - Alan Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-06-22
        Library of Congress Music Division; accession of discs, final
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-06-28
      - Alan Lomax to Melvin C. Oathout, 1938-06-28
      - Melvin C. Oathout to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-28
      - Alan Lomax to John Hammond, 1938-06-28
      - Alan Lomax to Theodore Christian Blegen, 1938-06-29
        Minnesota Historical Society
      - Sol Babitz to Alan Lomax, 1938-06-29
      - Harold Spivacke to Melvin C. Oathout, 1938-06-30
      - Alan Lomax to Kay Dealy, 1938-06-30
      - Alan Lomax to William A. Myers, 1938-06-30
        Federal Writers' Project, Indiana
      - Ralph S. Boggs to Alan Lomax, 1938-06
    - July 1968 (Box-folder 4/135)
      - Alan Lomax to Samuel Clay Dixon, 1938-07-01, 2 copies
      - Alan Lomax to Marjorie Edgar, 1938-07-01
      - Alan Lomax to Art Ford, 1938-07-01
      - Alan Lomax to Charles Edward Brown, 1938-07-01
      - Alan Lomax to Paul G. Brewster, 1938-07-01, 2 copies
      - Alan Lomax to Eillism Schlecht, 1938-07-02, 2 copies
      - Alan Lomax to John W. Collier, 1938-07-02, 2 copies
      - Alan Lomax to Doyle Joyce, 1938-07-02
        Works Progress Administration, Federal Writers Project; 2 copies
      - Librarian of Congress to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-02
      - William Wolff to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-04
      - Melvin C. Oathout to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-07
      - Alan Lomax to Librarian of Congress, 1938-07-08
      - Rosa Warren Wilson to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-09
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Photostat, 1938-07-09
        Michigan and Wisconsin recording trip
      - John Krimsky to Harold Spivacke, 1938-07-11
      - A.J. Ford to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-11
        Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Alan Lomax to Sol Babitz, 1938-07-11
      - Alan Lomax to Theodore Christian Blegen, 1938-07-11
        Minnesota Historical Society; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Charles Edward Brown to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-11
        Director, Wisconsin State Historical Museum; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Alan Lomax to Marjorie Edgar, 1938-07-12
      - Alan Lomax to Middleton, C.A., 1938-07-12
      - David M. Bull to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-12
        Citywide Sound Service; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - George Palmer Putnam to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-13
      - Elizabeth Meyer to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-14
        U.S. Department of Agriculture, Farm Security Administration
      - Theodore Christian Blegen to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-14
      - Alan Lomax to Rosa Warren Wilson, 1938-07-18
        nos 2013-04-19
      - Olin Downes to Harold Spivacke, 1938-07-18
      - Olin Downes to Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge, 1938-07-18
      - Alan Lomax to Herbert Rollins, 1938-07-18
        Lomax plans to leave Washington for Michigan "this Friday".
      - Alan Lomax to Charles Edward Brown, 1938-07-18
      - Kay Dealy to Alan Lomax, 1938-07-19
      - Alan Lomax to Kimball Young, 1938-07-19
      - Alan Lomax to Esther Bell Beachy, 1938-07-19
        San Antonio Speech Arts Association
      - Alan Lomax to Robert D. MacKenzie, 1938-07-19
      - Alan Lomax to George Palmer Putnam, 1938-07-21
      - Alan Lomax to Olin Downes, 1938-07-21
      - George Palmer Putnam to Harold Spivacke, 1938-07-25
      - Harold Spivacke to George Palmer Putnam, 1938-07-29
      - Harold Spivacke to Olin Downes, 1938-07-29
      - Davidson Taylor to Alan Lomax, 1939-07-07
        Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc.
      - Davidson Taylor to Alan Lomax, 1939-07-18
    - August 1938 (Box-folder 4/136)
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Disbursing Office, 1938-08-01
      - Oscar Parks to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-01
        Indiana 1938 recording trip
      - George Palmer Putnam to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-02
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-02
        Telegram; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - J. D. Newsome to Mr. C. Kaldor, 1938-08-02
        Letter of introduction; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Herbert Putnam to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-02
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-03
        Hotel Montcalm, Detroit, with note on back; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Mary O. Eddy to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-04
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-04, 2 copies
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; New York World's Fair
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1938-08-06
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-10
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-10
      - William A. Myers to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-10
        Federal Writers' Project; Indiana 1938 recording trip
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-10
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-11
        Stolen disc recorder in Detroit, Michigan; Michigan 1938 recording trip; New York World's Fair
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-12
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-13
      - Elizabeth M. Wood to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-13
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-15, 2 copies
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-15
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-15
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; precise date uncertain
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-16
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-16
        Annual report; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-17
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-17
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; Presto machine recommendations
      - Alan Lomax to Davidson Taylor, 1938-08-17
      - Mary O. Eddy to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-18
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-18
      - Alan Lomax to William A. Myers, 1938-08-18
        Indiana Federal Writers Project; Indiana 1938 recording trip
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-20
        Postcard; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Oskar Parks to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-22
      - Sterling Fisher to Alan Lomax, 1938-08-25
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-08-27
    - September 1938 (Box-folder 4/137)
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-01
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-01
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-02, 2 copies
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1938-09-02
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-06, 2 copies
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Chief Clerk, 1938-09-06
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; 2 copies
      - Montana McDonald to John A. Lomax, 1938-09-06
        Answered by Alan Lomax
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-07
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-08
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-12
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-12
      - Samuel T. Burkhard to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-12
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-12
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-12
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-12
        Photostat of telegram with annotations; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Harold Spivacke to Elizabeth Meyer, 1938-09-14
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-16, 2 copies
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-17
      - Thomas J. Outram to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-18
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-19
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-21
      - Theodore Christian Blegen to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-23
      - Edward N. Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-24
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-26
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-09-28
        Telegram and 2 photostats; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Edward N. Waters to postmaster, Ironwood, Michigan, 1938-09-28
      - Edward N. Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-29
      - John S. Bugas to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-29
        FBI; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Edward N. Waters to Library of Congress Disbursing Office, 1938-09-29
      - Florence Dean Stryker to Alan Lomax, 1938-09-29
        Letter and two enclosures
    - October 1938 (Box-folder 4/138)
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-01
      - Edward N. Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-01
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1938-10-03
      - Edward N. Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-03
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-03
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; Letter dated 1938-10-30, but it must be the 3rd
      - Alan Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-10-04
      - Alan Lomax to Library of Congress Mail and Delivery Division, 1938-10-04
        Bill of lading; Michigan 1938 recording trip
      - Harold Spivacke to Elizabeth Meyer, 1938-10-04
        United States Film Service
      - Elizabeth Meyer to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-05
      - Felix Greene to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-05
      - Felix Greene to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-05
      - Harold Spivacke to Library of Congress Mail Division, 1938-10-06
      - Harold Spivacke to Felix Greene, 1938-10-07
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-08
      - Alan Lomax to Edward N. Waters, 1938-10-08
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-08
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-15
      - Ruth R. Roark to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-17
        Farmer Collett; Kentucky 1937 recording trip
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-19
      - Lilian Forster to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-20
      - Harold Spivacke to Felix Greene, 1938-10-21
      - Harold Spivacke to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-22
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-23
      - Felix Greene to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-24
      - Edward N. Waters to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-24
      - Alan Lomax to Harold Spivacke, 1938-10-25
      - Anne Scott West to Alan Lomax, 1938-10-31
    - November 1938 (Box-folder 4/139)
      - Alan Lomax to William A. Myers, 1938-11-07
      - Alan Lomax to Mason Palmer, 1938-11-07
      - Alan Lomax to Ruth R. Roark, 1938-11-08
      - Alan Lomax to John Green, 1938-11-08
      - Alan Lomax to Anne Scott West, 1938-11-10
      - William A. Myers to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-10
      - Alan Lomax to Forster Family, 1938-11-11
      - Myrtle Forster to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-12
      - Calvin Frazier to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-13
      - Olin Downes to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-14
      - Forster Family to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-16
      - Alan Lomax to Esther Bell Beachy, 1938-11-18
      - Alan Lomax to Thomas J. Outram, 1938-11-21
      - Annette Ebsen to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-21
      - Alan Lomax to E.C. Beck, 1938-11-22
        Michigan 1938 recording trip; Central State Teachers College (Michigan)
      - Alan Lomax to Calvin Frazier, 1938-11-22
      - Forster Family to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-23
      - Esther Bell Beachy to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-26
      - E.C. Beck to Alan Lomax, 1938-11-28